OneGuide on Xbox One gives you lots of ways to find shows you want to watch.
If OneGuide is one of your Most Recently Used apps on Home,
launch TV directly to the last channel you watched
or open the listings and see what’s on.
Get some help picking a show by pressing the Menu button
on your controller to open the OneGuide menu.
The menu gives you quick access to TV listings, trending, and favorites.
Trending lists the most popular shows being watched right now,
and also what’s trending based on Twitter activity.
Press the Menu button and choose Favorites to see
just the channels you’ve marked as favorites.
Add to Favorites by selecting the star by the channel name in the listings.
While you’re watching, you can still press the Menu button
to open the menu for browsing.
Or press X to jump back to where you were last in OneGuide.
Press up or down on your controller’s D-pad to open the Miniguide.
The Miniguide shows you what’s on the other channels.
Move right for details on a show, and move left to filter the channel list.
The top filter is All Channels. Below that is your most recent channels.
And below that is just the channels you’ve marked as favorites.
If you have Kinect, use voice commands to watch TV,
snap TV, or watch a specific channel by name.
If the OneGuide app isn’t your Most Recently Used list,
get started by going to the OneGuide hub.
Here you can jump into the top trending TV shows,
or launch TV to your most recent channel.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.